<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Algonotion</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Algonotion</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 12:54:35 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Career Options for Math majors</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/math_career_options/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 12:54:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/math_career_options/</guid>
      
      <description>Career options for math majors During my first year of university, I was really conflicted between majoring in physics vs mathematics. So, I ended up doing some research into the career options that maybe available after majoring in mathematics.
Different career paths research Mathematical physicist Data Analytics and data science machine learning (could be counted under data science) finance related fields financial analyst actuary investment banker insurance software engineering computer scientist Military/defense industry Military intelligence Combat engineer etc Game development Oil/Gas/Power industry Computer engineering cyber security Predictive modeling hydrology Cryptography adjunct instructor Algorithm optimization/development operations research analyst Engineering jobs pilot Operations Research Conclusion It is important to note that these are not garanteed career options.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pages/about/</guid>
      
      <description>This is a personal blog about topics that interest me. I usually cover topics that I&amp;rsquo;m learning or something that I have learnt in the past. The purpose of writing this is to mainly help me find gaps in my knowledge while also sharing knowledge with others who are interested in such topics.
The topics I cover ranges over from Mathematics, Physics, Programming, Electronics and to Embedded systems. I may even cover other topics that I find interesting.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
